Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
I'm Teresa Ikeda from Nogizaka46.
I'm Arno Nakanishi.
Hello, hello.
They're here.
This way.
This way, please.
We're here at the Laughing Art Mansion and the Ten by Ten.
This looks interesting.
It has something to do with the show "Gage-san-temi-temi" (What I'm doing right now, Gage-san is watching).
You see my autograph here? Oh, and Hina Higuchi's too!
Hinachiman's is here too. Let's go inside.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to say "bloglet" or "boo boo" but I'll say this... the best one I've had today is 20 bucks.
TERU KIM Shunyu, fb, look at me, dog!
Oh, Ikeda Teresa wrote the main story. This is a T-shirt.
Yes, I designed this T-shirt.
You did?
Yes, I did.
It's cute.
It comes with a badge, too. This time.
Arno's badge.
Mine is attached, too.
It's cute. Arno's choice.
It looks a little too cold.
It looks a little too cold. Does it look cold?
What's wrong? No sense of the season.
There are a lot of pictures of Teresa Ikeda.
Yes, there are.
What have you seen so far? The works that actually appeared in the show are lined up.
The strong win the battle. The patient one is Higuchi.
Heh.
He's a comedian who slips and slides, but rises to his feet with the force of his slip.
He's a main tender like Mitsuo-san.
Teresa's.
I drew that. I'm so embarrassed.
It's amazing.
People who are good at drawing are good at capturing shapes, aren't they?
You can make Kotoge-san's face with paper and origami.
This is a chance to show off my dexterity.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to bring it with me.
I'll bring it with me.
Bleu-Be and Y-Be.
Yes, Yebe.
I have an impression that I'm a little bit yibe.
I'll fold it in half for now.
You have really beautiful big bones.
Really?
Yes, it is.
I'm looking at it here, and it's really rounded at the back.
I envy you, you have a rounded back of your head.
But it's coming. It's coming.
They're coming, they're coming.
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
It's done. This way.
This is Brubenokotouge. A little bit orange. It's quite orangey. It's a nice color.
But it's beautiful. It's quite beautiful. I wonder if it's called a koban shape.
The skull is beautiful. You're really good. Well then, may I go? Please go ahead.
There you go. Can you see what I mean? It's too asymmetrical. You're a fair-skinned person, aren't you? The back is pretty bad, too,
I'm not good at selling papers. Okay, let's go to the next room.
There are a lot of microwave ovens and so on. This is the Laughable Art Award 2023. I won the grand prize for this.
Lentil theater.
It's amazing.
It's dancing. It's like fried rice.
You mean like that? You mean "para para" in "para para fried rice"? I see. Interesting.
I heard that you can decide the title of this picture by yourself.
I see. I'd love to see you try it.
It is a test of taste, isn't it? It's difficult.
Post. There it is.
It's a sad monster.
Actually, this guy has a good heart. I see, it's kind of sad.
I like it. It's a good name, isn't it?
Please put a phrase on it to make it look like a LINE stamp.
Like, "Give me back my line," or something.
What's this? It's cute.
Recipe for sleep. What is this?
It's a work by Supermarket Kakamu, isn't it? Oh, wow. A bed? A bed. Yes, you can actually ride on it. Oh, you can? Okay, then.
You can go live on it. May I? Go ahead.
I have a camera. Here we go.
Wow!
He's getting tired.
Ah. We have tomatoes, too.
Oh, thank you. Oh, cucumbers. Cucumbers. Cucumbers.
Wow, thank you. I'll put some meat on it, too. It's all going to go on there.
Oh, wow. Oh, great. Oh, it's so comfy. I can sleep.
Does it look good?
Next, Michiru. I love the petit petit that helps me kill time.
I can kill time. I have a lot of free time. All of them. I'm bored all the time. Busy, busy, busy, busy.
Folded sticky note. What?
Really? Whoever came up with that was a genius, right? A lizard pencil sharpener. What?
When you sharpen the pencil, the lizard turns into a shrimp-roll lizard. Is this genius?
Isn't this the work of a genius?
This is the most fascinating thing I've seen today. It turns into a shrimp-roll lizard when you sharpen it.
Shouldn't this be a commercial product? This is so cute. It's so cute. I want one. Here it is. I want it.
Finally, it's all sitting on my liver. You can sit down. Start sitting down. Oh, can I sit down? Okay, then. Go ahead.
He said not to lean on it. That's great. Oh, wow. You've got guts? I've got guts!
It's here, it's here. I'm going to be able to do the live show at this rate. What is this? What is this?
Oh, waste of time. What? What?
I'm glad. I've been watching this on X for a long time. I'm so excited.
May I? Yes, I'm good. Here you go. Here we go.
Here it comes. I'm here. I'm here. Wow, it moved, it moved, it moved. It's the one I used to see on Twitter.
I feel like I'm looking at a pet.
Where the hell are you?
Oh, I'm lucky!
There are so many different variations.
I'm so happy to see you.
I didn't expect to find you here.
Thank you very much.
This is Kazuya Ishikawa.
Salaryman eraser.
It's going to peel off and the head is going to be scraped off, isn't it? This one
Kushir that becomes a tosaka
Cute!
Goat sponge that turns into a sheep
So cute!
I want one so bad!
I know.
Let's go to the next room!
This is Mr. Kazu Laser's room.
Want to try?
You want to try?
They're going to set it right here.
Oh, I'm waiting for it.
If I can do it, if I can do it, my legs are so long.
Are they supposed to be really soft? Yeah, he's like super soft.
Oh, oh, oh.
Spoiler alert!
Oh, my God, her legs are so long.
Next, we'll go to Mr. Hiccolohee's room.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Oh, what a stylish Hiko LOHEI!
What's this?
In the phone booth...
A phone number that goes up.
Any problems right now?
Troubles? I'm having a really bad day. Yeah.
Can I call my dream bracelet?
Or what?
"FUKUKOI FUKUKUKOI." FUKUKUKOI FUKUKUKOI.
Got it.
Got it? Yeah, I got it.
Yeah.
What? What, what, what, what?
It's off.
What's wrong?
Well, I've been invited to a very nice church.
A cult?
Yes, sir.
I can only read it in Teresa's expression.
I can't read it.
This is the merchandise area.
Let's go in.
Wow.
Teresa designed the merchandise.
This is the one we're wearing right now.
There's also this T-shirt and a badge.
I designed them.
We have tote bags.
We have T-shirts.
We also have random clear key chains.
I'm tempted to open one of the random series.
Do you want to open one?
Shall we open one?
Okay, then.
Here it comes!
Still no sign of them.
There it is, the manta ray.
It's so cute!
There it is... so cute!
Here we go!
Oh, my God!
It's a loaf of bread from Telepan!
It's true!
Yay!
That's cute too!
That's cute, too.
And I slept okay, so...
And...
I have good memories.
I have a memory.
Iroha... recently...
She gave me a bread key chain to wear.
I see.
There are three kinds of badge sets.
That's right.
They're slightly different.
Yeah, we actually bought about nine of them, so...
So this is what we got?
They made all these goods for us.
Please wear them.
Please get it!
Let's get it out.
Please let me out!
But I can't give it a bad title, can I?
It determines whether my work will be a great masterpiece or a lousy one.
I see... titles are important, aren't they?
It's done!
Theresa's work...
Here it is.
I see.
What do you think?
It's good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
They look alike, but...
But I feel like they have their own personalities.
What should I title it?
It'll determine the value of this picture.
Will it be worth it?
It's worth it.
Tsk.
Oh!
Yee!
Twin Ray.
Twin Ray, I'm here.
It's a chunk of my soul.
It's a little bit like a twin ray, isn't it?
How was it? This time...
It was a lot of fun.
We also made this big twin ray.
And this one, too... will be displayed here.
I'm so happy!
And we have T-shirts.
We'll have T-shirts and lots of other goodies.
Please come to Coquila.
Please come to Kokila and see all of our works!
Please subscribe to our channel!
And please click the "Good" button!
This is Ikira. This is Nakanishi.
See you soon!
Subtitles by Ishinokami